He wanted to fight D Green one time.
>> No, he he wanted to fight everybody
>> because the the freakish athletes,
they going to be coming off the board.
>> We're on the course. Who be your caddy?
>> Bluefoot.
Coming up on the Get Loud podcast. We
are talking to a legend, Hall of Famer.
My homeboy Champ Bailey. Champs in the
house. Of course, plenty of draft talk.
Should we trade down? Should we stay
where we are? Uh, put that car in
reverse.
>> And also, it's your birthday week. It's
my birthday. It's my birthday. It's my
birthday.
Welcome inside the Big Bear AI Command
Center Studio. It is the Get Loud
podcast presented by SeatGeek, the
official primary ticketing partner of
the Washington Commanders. Buying
tickets to Commanders games and more at
SeatGeek. My man Fred Smooth. What's up,
brother?
>> I'm waking up, man. I'm loving the I
guess that's called fuchsia.
>> Fuchsia.
>> Is that the color fuchsia right there?
>> Sort of a salmon.
>> A blush pink.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You know what I'm saying?
It's very springy.
>> Oh, I'm ready for spring.
>> Very springy,
>> man. Thank you, man.
>> Listen, I give you props, man.
>> I appreciate you, man. How's your
weekend?
>> My weekend was great cuz the weather was
great. I'm more one of these people I
mock the weather. If the weather's good,
I'm good. And listen, just got out, took
a long walk. You don't know how much you
miss that son until you hit you. You
like, you know what? This is what it's
to feel like every day.
>> It's going to be a great show. We got
Champ Bailey coming up later on. Champ.
>> Oh my god.
>> My guy.
>> Nice job pulling him in, man.
>> My first running mate, man. When I first
got here, it was me and Champ, man. That
was my dude all the time. Been my dude
since day one. That's I can't wait to
talk to him.
>> One of the greats. Also, we want to hear
from you. So, you can email us
watchtowoud@gmail.com.
You can call us 7037267419.
Also, a couple of big announcements. So,
first of all, uniform reveal taking
place tomorrow.
>> Franklin Hall.
>> Yeah, come out. The whole crew is going
to be there. So, go to Franklin Hall. If
you can't make it,
>> it'll be on YouTube x Facebook as well.
And on YouTube, you know, you can click
that bell, little icon to let everyone
know we're live. If you can't make it
out there, you can see that. And also
next week, same deal when we're at
Northwest Stadium for the draft party.
>> The draft party should be off the chain.
>> Exactly. So come on out there again if
you can't make it. We're going to be
live on all the social media platforms.
So click that reminder so you can check
it out. We're looking forward to that.
I'm excited, man.
>> Yeah. Most It's that time of year like
the NFL has just found a way to take
over months that we just usually didn't.
this February, March, April, this this
Super Bowl, this uh combine, this draft.
It's just
>> NFL just the gift they keep on giving.
Do you remember the old You can see
these videos on like ESPN from like
>> a few decades ago when the draft was
like a bunch of dudes just sitting in a
room
>> and they had just like a regular
>> and then the name just pops up and that
was
>> like a bunch of cardboard names of
teams. Imagine being a football player.
Didn't probably have a TV. Don't even
know if you got drafted.
>> Yeah. You probably just got a phone
call.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You just like But it had to
be on the house phone.
>> You had to be at home to accept this
call. Yes. This is this is coach. I'm
like, "All right, let's just get this
thing going then, coach." Cuz that's how
they started off. Hey, is this Fred?
>> Yeah, this Fred. Yeah, this coach Marty
Shenheimer. Welcome to the Washington
thing. I like wow him
>> right there.
>> It's amazing how it's grown. Like not
only is the event massive, then we talk
about it for weeks.
>> Well, it's it's it's taken on a life of
its own.
>> Yeah, it really has.
>> It it's taken on a life of its own. And
it it has went from what I think it used
to be all together one day in the 80s.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah. NOW IT'S THREE DAYS.
>> And you know what's going to happen as
soon as this draft is over? Like the
next day you'll get a headline on your
phone or a notification like the all too
early 2020
draft pick.
>> Yes. Yes. That just tells you. It just
24-hour news, sir.
>> All the time. It It never stops. Never
stops.
>> Look at this. So, you have a great event
coming up.
>> STOP. HEY. WHY YOU WHY YOU LAUGHING AT
THE PICTURE, MAN?
>> Because the picture is with when I
looked at it. You have You have to tell
us about this event. But I saw you and I
was like, "Who else?" Oh, it's Fred with
Fred. You
>> put nobody else and you.
>> IT'S MY GOLF TOUR.
>> IT LOOKS GREAT. BUT I'M LIKE, "COME OUT
WITH Fred and also Fred."
>> Now, listen to me. This This is the
first Wolf draft that I put out before I
put all the names of the player that's
going to be on there because I got tons
of football players coming and it's it's
going to be fun, man. It's going to be
May 4th at 1757 right here in Ashurn. It
it
>> the best golf tournament you can go to.
It's Fred Smoot's golf tournament. If
you want to have fun and see I turn to
Smoot D Shambo when I get them clubs in
my hand. All right. So, it's going to be
what I say is going to be a very, very
fun day. From the inception to the
reception, it's going to be fun.
>> And I was looking at this. You've got
some big names coming out, too.
>> Oh, no. I got some guys coming out. I
got legends. I got a couple of Hall of
Famers coming out. Like I said, if you
want to golf with one of your favorite
players, present, maybe past players.
This is your chance right here.
>> And it benefits a great cause.
>> Oh, most definitely. The Bridge of Life
Foundation. Most definitely. Uh, I lost
my mom to cancer. cancer touches all of
us in some form and fashion. Also, I'm a
big component when it comes to the
military. So, we do a lot for retirees
and stuff like that. So, yeah, bridge of
life is for just what it says to bridge
the life.
>> Yeah. Well, good on you for doing that.
And it's the best of both worlds. Meet
some legends, including yourself. And
being out there means you're going to
benefit people who have suffered from
cancer. So, it's wonderful on both ends.
>> Wait,
>> what?
>> It's your birthday.
>> It is my birthday.
>> Today is today.
>> No, no, it's not today. It's Friday.
>> Okay.
>> My birthday is Friday, April 17th.
>> And the funny part about it, when I got
drafted, I think I got drafted April
18th.
>> So, I got drafted like the day after my
birthday. Party.
>> Yeah. So, most definitely. So, most
definitely. I'm going to enjoy Friday.
Friday is going to be a great day. The
weekend belongs to me, Jinx.
>> I believe this.
>> The weekend belongs to me.
>> You have plans?
>> Yes, I do. I'mma come down to PTOIC like
George was.
>> Oh, here we go then.
ROLL ON UP.
>> Slide on up to the top.
>> I'm coming down a pomic like George.
>> Well, today is the lovely Catherine's
birthday. And I say that because
yesterday we woke up and I'm expecting
like a lazy Sunday.
>> Yeah.
>> Next thing I know, 8 hours later,
>> we had a Sunday funday celebration cuz
she was like, "It's my birthday.
Tomorrow's Monday. I got to celebrate
now."
>> I I you know what? I know why I love
Katherine cuz she Aries. That's why
that's why we got that Kendrick spirit.
We got that Kendrick spirit. That fire
is different, man. Like you a Aries is
different, man. I tell people all the
time, man. It see how you feel that your
girl is a alpha.
>> I mean, that's what I love about her,
though. I mean, she's fiery
>> cuz everything starts with Aries.
>> I always say she's two steps away from a
fight.
>> YOU TELL ME THIS.
>> NOT WITH ME. YOU TELL ME THIS.
>> NOT WITH ME. I'M LIKE, OH GOD. I'M LIKE,
SAY one more thing.
Aries Aries, we don't back down,
>> right? No,
>> we we don't back down from any of
anything. And we got the purest stone of
>> all all months. It's the diamond.
>> Oh god. That's right. It's the best one.
>> It's the cuz we are the start of the
zodiac calendar. The zodiac calendar
starts with Aries. All right. That's why
we the alpha to the omega.
>> Let me ask you this. I'll ask Anna's
here as well. Anna, so how much do you
believe it? Because you hear people all
the time like, "Oh my god,
>> the uh Jupiter is in whatever. I don't
know." Right. The alliance or or how
different planets align or your zodiac
sign and how that affects your being or
what happens to you. I'm not really into
that. Are you into that
>> astrology? No. No. Santana is big in Is
he lives by it?
>> You always feel like Mercury's in
retrograde.
>> Santana Gemini. So he always say it's
two sides to me.
>> Oh, okay.
>> All right. So most definitely. I'm not
one of them people. I don't really buy
into it until it's convenient.
>> Right. So, I don't really buy into it
because I don't think the month you born
in dictate the type of person you are,
>> right?
>> Because I My mom could have slipped and
fell AND HAD ME TWO WEEKS EARLIER.
>> YEAH.
>> I WOULD HAVE BEEN THE SAME PERSON,
WOULDN'T I? YEAH. Has to be.
>> Yeah. I feel like I do feel like some of
my personality traits align with being a
Leo, but I don't know all of it if it's
all me.
>> But if I throw enough stuff against the
wall, some stuff going to stick to you,
>> right? But I also it's entertaining.
It's fun to ask like it's fun to ask
like you know ask people what their
zodiac is and then you're like oh are we
supposed to be friends or not?
>> But also at the same time I'm like I'm
going to be friends with anybody
regardless.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So it it doesn't really
>> it's like reading your horoscope is like
a new opportunity will present itself
and then you get like an online coupon
code. You're like look at that
opportunity
just like my horoscope said.
>> You're waiting on something to fall out
the sky.
>> Totally self-fulfilling prophecy. This
month right here, you will find
>> nothing but wealth and luxury.
>> WHERE WHERE THAT LIKE NO, I DON'T I
don't put it like this. I don't live by
it.
>> Yeah.
>> I entertain it, but I don't put any
stock in it. Any stock at all. What's
your sign, Jinx?
>> I'm Sagittarius.
>> Oh.
>> Anything special about a Sagittarius? I
DON'T KNOW.
>> WE'RE SUPPOSED TO be independent, you
know, likes others, gets along with
others.
Isn't it like a Oh god, I don't know.
Was it a topaz? Maybe. I think that's
wrong. I'm not sure.
>> Nobody.
>> I don't know.
>> I will say one time I did go to a
fortune teller.
>> Yeah,
>> this is you.
>> Oh man,
>> I've had a bad experience with that.
>> You did?
>> I shouldn't have gone
>> years ago in Deont Circle. I think she's
still around. And so I go and you just
like walk in upstairs and this guy
answers like, "Let me see if she's
feeling all right. Is she still
connected?" Right.
>> So just creepy.
>> She comes out. She's like, "Yeah, I can
do a reading." And so she's doing tarot
cards and she goes, she's snap. She
goes, "You like your job. You're good at
your job. You're going to get a
promotion in one year." And I was like,
"Okay, a year to the week.
>> You got a promotion."
>> I My boss called me in. That's the only
time that he called me into the
conference room and he was like, "The
10:00 show, you've wanted it, it's
yours. Do whatever you want to, but it
it's yours." And I was like, I'm got a
huge pro a week like and and all you
could think about in your head was Madam
Cleo.
>> YES. CALL ME NOW.
>> THAT'S ALL you can think about was she
told me
>> it was crazy.
>> Yeah.
>> But you never know. I mean, some of that
stuff could be coincidence, too.
>> Well, she was right. I DIDN'T YOU CAN
SAY WHAT YOU WANT TO,
>> but she was right.
>> She was right about what she said. And
she said it within a year. She did it
and within
>> I mean, it was crazy. Anna, you want to
share this terrible story?
>> I had a really Okay, I don't go after
that experience. I was like, "This is
bad stuff. Gotta stay away." They were
too right. And I just felt like that
that's some dark energy. Like, you don't
want to be near it. I would say I would
actually warn people against it.
>> Now, I'm going to be all IN GEORGETOWN.
I GOT
>> I GOT THE AFTERNOON OFF. I MIGHT text
you guys later.
>> Well, with death in life, I think we
should bring it back to Fred's birthday.
I have a birthday PRESENT FOR YOU.
>> OH, REALLY?
>> A BIRTHDAY SURPRISE. And my birthday
present to you is that I'm not putting a
timer on headlines anymore.
>> That's terrible.
>> I'm not doing it.
>> You are a terrible gift.
>> I stopped because this is a gift to you
and the fans. So, thank you.
>> I'm sorry. The fans hated the clock.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Well, I guess. Thank you.
>> You're welcome.
>> Wow.
>> That was the worst.
>> I'm not even going to tell the story.
>> That's the worst gift I ever got.
>> Well, we're talking about golf. What do
you think about the Masters? How about
Roy? Two in a row now. back to back. HE
LIKE THE DODGERS RIGHT NOW. Uh
>> once he had that weight lifted, like
different dude.
>> He seems happier right now.
>> Yeah. And that's what it is about
golfers, man. They need to like they
home life need to be in order for them
to really play their sport, to really be
focused on their sport. And and you
know, like any golfing trip,
>> it's you against the course. It ain't
you against the other guys. Yeah.
>> It's you against the course. And and
right now Rory seemed to have this
course ripped around his finger right
now.
>> He said something really interesting
which was because last year obviously he
was waiting on he was trying to complete
the career grand slam and he did and he
said you know I thought that last year I
thought it's so hard to complete the
grand slam at the Masters. He goes and
now I realize no no no it's just hard to
win the Masters. It's just hard to win.
It's just hard to win the Masters.
>> And that's what it's about. It's just
hard to win some places. I had a fan
reach out to me to tell me something
about uh
>> a golf a local golfer that we had from
here. Oh, really?
>> All right. Uh Leburg native, Michael
Brennan.
>> Okay.
>> A PGA tour rookie winner finished uh two
under part for his first masters.
>> Oh, wow.
>> Brennan was accomp I mean uh he uh was
accompanied by his golf instructor
that's at the golf course that I'm
throwing my golf tournament at. 1757.
All right. Adam Herel. All right. So,
and this guy's a local guy that went to
Farmwell Station where my kids went to
middle school, man.
>> Oh, wow. Okay.
>> And uh just showing the local guy some
love, man. Michael Brennan.
>> Well done.
>> How about that?
>> 200 Augusta.
>> Listen, hell yeah.
>> Anything under
>> if I if I went 10 over an Augusta, I'd
be I'd be telling everybody.
>> First of all, golfers make it look so
easy. But that's and that's the thing is
that if you play golf, you know, you
know, like that might look easy, but
that's the point. It's so difficult.
>> They do it in three, they do it in three
shots,
>> right?
>> The normal person probably have to do it
in six.
>> Oh my gosh. Like it's just not easy what
they do. But all sports, all people that
play high-end sports make it look easy.
Football players make football LOOK
EASY. IT'S NOT. NO.
>> It's a very hard sport, man.
>> If you were on the course, who would be
your caddy?
>> Bluefoot.
That's what I thought you were going to
say. Blue foot. You say Sean.
>> Yeah. Blue foot. You know Sean been my
sidekick my most of my life.
>> DOES HE PLAY? HE PLAYS GOLF, doesn't he?
>> I don't. Or does he?
>> I think Sean can play. He's a lefty.
>> Oh, is he?
>> Yeah. So So Sean is a lefty.
>> Okay.
>> So yeah, I think Blue Foot can swing him
pretty good.
>> All right.
>> Yeah, but yeah, Bluefoot London will
probably be my my caddy. And what I
think what we don't think and get these
golfers props for cuz when I play 18
hoes, I'm exhausted by the end of the
day.
>> They walk the course.
>> Yeah, they walk the course. Well, I you
know, I was trying to tell someone, we
were having debates on this. This is
about Tiger a few months ago and they're
like, "Yeah, but if Tiger gets on the
course, I'm like, but the thing is he
almost lost his leg and I know he's
going through it right now going to
rehab and everything, so wish him the
best." But I'm like, it's hard enough to
walk 18 with that sort of physical and
mental focus. Imagine walking on a leg
where he has a permanent leg. It don't
work.
>> It takes takes him completely out
>> out of out of the game. Like that's
that's why they say that you got to have
a good caddy now.
>> Yeah.
>> Got to have a good caddy cuz I couldn't
imagine carrying my own clubs.
>> Oh, no. No. Listen, I just can't.
>> What do you guys think about Rory
blowing that six point lead? I don't
know how to talk about golf. Six.
six lead like that was shocking. He was
>> No, no, it ain't shocking.
>> Making history and then
>> no golf is like that
>> a little bit. He won the Masters for the
Golf takes turns.
>> I mean the thing about at any other
course or at a lot of courses I mean a
six shot lead no one has had that big of
a lead after 36 the Masters ever and it
looked like he was just unstoppable run
away with it.
>> But the thing about Augusta which is so
fascinating is that the best in the
world all it takes is a hole or two
>> and get stuck. Yeah. He just couldn't
get out of his way in the
>> Listen and I know they got to be
frustrating to get in the hole and you
you think this is a two, three, four
stroke hole and now you had six seven
stroke that that's that's different.
>> I mean even on the final hole, you know,
I mean he had what a two shot lead and
so but then he goes right like way into
the pine straw and it's like he's going
to make this dicey.
>> Yeah.
>> Even at the end it was like I don't
know.
>> It's you against the course. All right.
never against the the the players. It's
you against the courts and it can get
ugly. Some days I'm out there, I feel
like this game was meant for me. Some
days I get out there, I never played
before in my life. God, you know, he
said the most baller thing that made me
so jealous. I think it was after the
first I think it was after the first
round and he was being interviewed and
he was like, "Yeah, I think I'm just
going to go I'm going to go put on my
green jacket and just have a drink." AND
I WAS LIKE,
>> "OKAY, RORY." I mean, I had to do the
same thing, but I was like, that's
quiet. This baller thing I've heard, you
know, just give me the green jacket.
Same one you gave me last year. Pour me
a drink, please. Put on my green.
>> You know my size.
>> Wow.
>> That mean must be nice.
>> Yeah. Hey, listen, man. Were you a
baller? You got that confidence in him?
>> Good for you, man.
>> He's the best golfer in the world right
now.
>> Yeah, he's awesome.
>> Ain't nothing you could do.
>> So, let's talk a little football on this
show since we got Champ coming up, we
got the draft coming up, we got the
uniform reveal tomorrow again, Franklin
Hall. So come out, check that out if you
want to.
Which quarterback, this is an
interesting question. So thank you Anna
for putting this in the rundown. Which
quarterback is under the most pressure
in 2026?
>> Quarterback.
>> The hottest seat in the NFL.
I hate to say this considering that this
guy won a Super Bowl just a couple of
years ago. Jaylen Herz. Okay. Uh,
Philadelphia is loud and right now
>> they've already like kind of like like
kicking him out.
>> NO, NO, NO. THEY ALREADY positioning
themselves to say
is it reminding you of Russell Wilson?
It's giving off very Russell Wilson
Seattle
>> like when he Okay.
>> All right. All right. Seattle wins the
Super Bowl. We know it's because of the
the the Legion of Doom and Maron Lynch.
Russell get all the accolades.
>> I mean, he is a Hall of Famer,
>> is he?
>> Yes. Russell Wilson will be a Hall of
Famer,
>> is he?
>> Yes.
>> You don't think the last four or five
years?
>> See, I've had this What has happened in
the last four means nothing?
>> There's this whole new I feel like
there's this whole new mindset that
suddenly what you do at the end takes
away from your if you've won.
>> It's how you exit the game.
>> Yes. Do you know how many Do you know
how many players have exited the game
limping off playing terribly? I
>> did you know Joe Nameoth like finished
his career like the Rams?
>> I listen let me ask you something then.
Is Eli Mann in the Hall of Fame?
>> He will get in the Hall of Fame. I think
he's you can make a strong case that
he's borderline but two Super Bowls and
beating those Patriots teams.
>> All right. And we talking about him
limping in. Right.
>> Right.
>> About 20 ballots from now. All right.
If Eli just getting in there, one time
Super Bowl winner and Super Bowl loser,
Russell Wilson.
>> Yeah, but if you look at his career
stats, like people, I get it. You saw
what happened in Denver. He's been
bouncing around since then. He's not the
same guy, but based on what he did in
Seattle, people freak, for a long time,
he was a top five quarterback easy in
the NFL.
>> All I'm saying is
>> And he's got a ring.
>> He got a ring, but so does Trent Der.
>> Oh, come on. I all I'm saying is this
man
>> Russell Wilson might be the most
controversial
>> Hall of Fame if
>> you you know you sound like Richard
Sherman. Didn't Richard Sherman say the
same thing?
>> I'm I'm JUST TELL I'M WITH RICHARD. LIKE
AT THE END OF THE day I don't know if
he's a Hall of Famer. I really don't
know if if Russell has done enough to
win a Hall of Fame cuz one Super Bowl
ain't going to just get you in there.
Now, if you've done what he's done, his
totality of work. All right, let's look
at his stats right now, right? We know
he is a Super Bowl champion.
>> Yeah,
>> he's a 10 time Pro Bowler.
>> He's a 10 time.
>> And first of all, we don't really count
these Pro Bowls no more cuz they giving
them OUT LIKE CHEESE. SHORA SANDERS IS A
ONE time Pro Bowl,
>> right? But also, they weren't doing that
when he was making Pro Bowls. Yeah, he
got like three of those in there that
just
>> if he has seven Pro Bowls, a 10 time Pro
Bowler and Super Bowl champion and God
knows how many records he has set in
Seattle.
>> All right. Is Jaylen Herz on a on a Hall
of Fame?
>> No,
>> they the same dude.
>> They might be, but Russell has
accomplished more. Jaylen had his mama
for a couple years, right? Jayen got as
many Super Bowls as Russell,
>> but that's not the only thing you take
into account. Or Trent Dilford would be
in the hall.
>> I listen,
>> a lot of dudes would be in the Nick Fos
is not going to make the hall, but he's
got a ring.
>> Most definitely. That's what I'm saying.
Everybody that wins a Super Bowl or go
to a Pro Bowl ain't going to the Hall of
Fame.
>> But a decade of Pro Bowls, all sorts of
Super Bowl record or a Seattle records
and a Super Bowl. I don't I'm not a Russ
apologist. Like I don't really like
Russell Wilson, but the numbers are the
number.
>> How much did he really do early?
>> He made 10 Pro Bowls, won a Super Bowl.
Also, that's the Legion of the Legion of
Boom was incredible. But let's not act
like Russell wasn't very good.
>> He was good. He wasn't great.
>> He was 10 time Pro Bowl great.
>> Stop. Stop doing that. Don't do that. Do
not do that.
>> We need to ask Chat GPT or Gemini.
>> No, I'm not asking a machine about
sports. Well, then you can get an
objective like, is Russell Wilson a Hall
of Famer?
>> Well,
>> I can't believe I'm defending Russ so
much. I don't even like Russ.
>> Listen, I'm just saying
that the politician known as Russell
Wilson, it it's going to be debatable.
That's all I'm saying.
>> How much do you think of this is because
people don't really like Russ?
>> A lot of it.
>> A LOT OF IT. YEAH.
>> THIS IS WHAT WE HAVE. THIS IS WHAT WE
HAVE. There's a case for and the case
against because it needs to be
>> Okay. Fair. Fair. Fair. Case four, Pro
Bowls, Super Bowl, statistical rankings,
and efficiency. He's fifth alltime in
passer rating. Case against, recent
struggles, lack of MVP votes. He's never
received the MVP vote, which is rare for
a modern era QB in the Hall of Fame,
>> no first team AllPro. He's never been
named a first team all pro and has only
one second team nod. And critics argue
he was never considered the absolute
best quarterback in the league during
his peak.
>> Yes.
>> So it's like Tom Brady,
>> but also you could say that like look at
Bill Bich. He was the best at the time.
>> No, Bill was the best of all time.
>> Best of all time. So that's why he
fame is so different than Russell
Wilson.
>> And that's why I say it's still that big
if with Russell. And I KNOW YOU DON'T
SEE IT.
>> I THINK IT'S because people don't like
him.
He's unlikable. I I get that.
>> Yeah.
>> But what I'm saying is it's it's some a
couple careers that I could like compare
to his career that's not too far from
each other. That's all I'm saying.
>> I mean, you can make a case against it.
Like I hate coming off as the Russell
Wilson apologist ON THIS SHOW.
>> NO, NO. I I TOTALLY UNDERSTAND HOW YOU
FEEL, but I just it's a if in there,
>> I guess. But if But if Okay, here's the
thing, too. If Eli gets in, and he's
gonna get in.
>> Well, Eli got the man
>> pedigree,
>> but he's getting Eli's getting in.
>> Eli got two Super Bowls.
>> But would you Let me ask you this. In
their primes,
>> who would I take?
>> Who would you take?
>> To win one game?
>> No. In their prime, you got to have one
quarterback. Who you taking? Russell or
Eli?
>> That's not That's a hard choice. Now,
>> okay.
>> Eli precision passer. uh know how to
lead. Both of them good leaderships.
>> I would think as a player I would get
along more with Eli.
>> You would? But is that who you would
choose?
>> Yeah, I want to get I want to get along
with my quarterback. I think I get along
with Eli and I think Russell rub me the
wrong way.
>> Yeah, you would hang out with Eli and
then Russ locker be like, "Yeah, man.
What's up?"
>> Yeah. I wouldn't say much to him. You
know what I'm saying?
>> So, I I would probably say Eli on that
one. I I hate to do it to you, but yeah.
No, that's I mean I gotta I gotta cut
myself off. I'm like I can only defend
Russ so much.
>> Broncos country.
>> That's right.
>> The worst slogan.
>> It left a room with crickets when he got
up there and said by golly.
>> I'm not doing that.
>> Let's ride.
>> I' I would have said, "Nah, I'm not
doing that."
>> It was the most cringiest
situation since the POLITICIAN DID THE
>> OH, WHAT'S HOWARD DEAN? YES.
>> GOD, WHERE DID that I can't believe I
PULLED THAT NAME. REMEMBER THAT? AND
WE'RE GOING TO GO TO KENTUCKY. AND WE'RE
GOING TO GO TO ALABAMA. AND WE'RE GOING
TO GO TO NEW HAMPSHIRE.
>> AND YOU KNOW what's funny is that now
THAT WOULDN'T
>> THAT WAS now
>> that that ruined that torpedoed his
campaign today. It wouldn't mean
anything.
>> It wouldn't mean anything.
>> People forget about it 24 hours. At the
time,
>> listen,
>> the sleeves rolled up.
part a part of me want to give Russ some
props first cuz I was like h I've never
heard a player say let's ride for the
Broncos. So I want to give him some some
props at first but then I was like
>> cringey.
>> This is cringey.
>> Have you ever done in your career like
cuz you've been a part of
>> Yeah. Well, not I mean where you were a
part of some sort of you know marketing
effort, a promo commercial and you're
like I don't know if I want to do that
or I should have done that
>> and and nothing that cringey.
>> Yeah, cuz that was super cringy.
>> That that's cringey because he also
tried to put his own spin
>> on the Broncos
>> that's been there for like a thousand
years, right?
>> So if John Elway didn't say let's ride,
you should never say let's ride. If
Terrell Dave didn't say let's ride,
never say let's ride.
>> Guys, give us a call 7037267419
or you can email us as always Washington
getloud@gmail.com.
If you go to a psychic and Georgetown,
let us know how that goes.
>> Yeah.
>> And don't forget,
we're going to have tomorrow Franklin
Hall in DC uniform reveal party. Check
that out. We're going to have the draft
party next Thursday, Northwest Stadium.
They both start at 7 o'clock. So, if you
can't make it, hit that bell on YouTube
to let you know when the coverage
starts. Also, follow us on Facebook and
X as well.
>> Well, we are not ones to throw out the
word legend too often on the show.
Living legend. Well, we got a living
legend right here. Of course, we're
talking about Champ Bailey, the Hall of
Famer, 12-time Pro Bowler, selected by
Washington, number seven overall back in
1999. Champ, thanks for being here. And
we've been talking about the draft and
what that moment was like for Fred when
he was drafted. What do you remember
from being drafted by this team in that
moment for you?
>> Wow, man. It was actually a crazy day.
And um you know, I think if you could
remember that was the year it was 99,
the year Ricky Williams got got drafted,
too. So, so if you remember how he got
drafted, you know, the Saints traded all
their draft picks
>> to move up to number five and they
traded them with the the Redskins.
>> And I thought I was going to be the
fifth pick, but I I understand the
Redskins position taking, you know, all
the draft picks and then eventually
moving back down to number seven, using
some of those draft picks to draft me.
So it it was just I knew I was going to
go to Washington, but at the same time,
you know, nothing's guaranteed when that
draft.
>> Yeah. In that draft, you just don't know
cuz things can change. And that was a
dramatic change. But that all started
when
>> uh Indianapolis Colts selected Edan
James
>> and then, you know, Mike Dicka just
said, "Man, hell with this. I'm going to
win." Yeah.
>> So, he traded all his draft picks for
that pick and he was the only draft pick
that year, I believe.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> For that team. But, you know, crazy
year, man. Crazy year.
>> I got to ask you cuz I've always told
the story about when I I got drafted and
I walked into the locker room, I mean,
to the DB room for the first time and I
got to see you Dale Green and Prime was
still here at the time and I'm like, I
don't know why they drafted me. How did
you feel when you walked in the locker?
I mean in in the DB meeting for the
first time and Dion and Dale Green was
in the room.
>> Well, well, let me let me remind you. It
was only Daryl at the time.
>> All right. All right. All right.
>> That was Yeah. Yeah. So, Dion came my
second year.
>> What was crazy is
>> Daryl was really my coach. Now, Tom
Hayes was the coach at the time, but he
always allowed me and Daryl to just go
sit in the corner and just talk. And
that's that's really when I first
learned how to play quarterback. Like I
just I was just being the best athlete
on the field. That's all I knew how to
do up until that point. And then I
became more of a technician learning
from him. But when Dion came in, hell,
you know, I come off a good rookie year.
>> But here comes Dion. And Dion's more my
body type, right? So I can really see,
>> you know, all the things he was talking
about in film, the things he was doing
in practice, you know, working on. I
tried to take all that. So, I got the
best of both worlds. I learned a lot
from Daryl Green that first year and
that continued till he retired. But then
I had Dion in the middle of that to kind
of show me, you know, in real time like
what it really means to be a big corner
cuz
>> Daryl was different. Daryl was small.
Daryl wasn't trying to touch nobody.
But, you know,
>> you know, at the line of scream, that's
just who he was. But he had great feet.
And I just learned, you know, that that
old saying he had, your hands are great,
but your feet are better. And he would
always harp on that. And man, I took
that I I took that to heart, boy. And
that's how I modeled my career.
>> I I remember you caught me uh studying
Daryl one day and you were like, "Hey
man, can't nobody Daryl Green but Daryl
Green." So, no, you need to you need to
study me a Dion or somebody like that.
But that just tell you when you run a
4240, you'll get out of uh trouble speed
like you don't have to be a good
technician.
>> No, he was just Oh, he was athletic,
fast as hell. I mean, dude, he was I
mean, he he was one of the best ever. I
mean, we we all know we all know what he
done. So, you know, to play at 40 the
way he did, that was crazy, dog.
>> Oh, yeah. It was crazy. It was crazy.
Like, to to just watching practice, I
remember I was watching both of y'all
and I just remember watching him
practice and I like in the back of my
mind, I was like, "This dude 40 years
old."
>> Like, I think I'm forgetting I'm
forgetting the fact that he's still the
fastest dude on the team and he's 40
years old. Unbelievable. And and he's
still trying to play flag football. I
don't know what's going on with D Green
right now,
>> man. When he told me that, I was like,
"What?" I mean, what? You pushing 70.
YOU BRO, what are you doing?
>> I I I can't even do it. And I ain't even
50 yet, you know? So,
More power to him, though. I got to give
him that.
>> Ch, you clearly made a name for yourself
for two different franchises. What What
do you remember from your time here in
DC?
>> You know, I I I gotta be honest. I
didn't want to leave, you know, but at
the time it it was obvious I had to
leave in order to maximize my career,
you know. That means the money I was
supposed to make,
>> the opportunities going to the playoffs,
potentially winning a Super Bowl or
having a chance, you know. So, it was
only fitting that I had to leave. I
mean, people don't understand like
there's so much about relationships in
football that matter. And y'all see it.
You see the coaching trees, you see how
all these coaches get job. It's all
relationship based, right? And people
vouching for you at the right time.
>> So to understand like Dan Snyder did not
draft me.
>> So
I believe I believe Chris Chris and and
uh Lavar got a a new deal and they were
drafted the year after me before I did.
Right. So
>> so the writing was on the wall like,
"Okay, they don't really want to pay
me." I mean, I asked for what I asked
for. They laughed at it. They offered me
something else. I said that same thing
to the Broncos and they was like, "Oh,
that's it."
>> And I like for more, you know. SO,
>> oh that's it. That's all THAT'S ALL I
WANT, MAN. YOU KNOW, MAKE ME HAPPY.
>> SO, so you got to understand the
dynamics there. I was not
>> I was a franchise. They franchised me,
but until I signed that tag, I could not
be traded.
>> Mhm. So, I had a lot of power in that
moment to dictate where I went. So,
there was two offers on the table. Well,
there was two teams on the table. They
the offer was pretty much the same thing
for both teams. And I just chose the
Broncos because I just I just love the
way they ran their program. And Shanahan
being the genius he was, it's like,
yeah, it's a no-brainer.
>> Well, LET ME COMPARE COMPARE THE CITIES
to for me. Compare Denver to the DMV. I
I BECAUSE I FEEL LIKE THE DMV JUST COME
UNDEFEATED, BABY.
>> UNDEFEATED. SO, I gota So, so you got to
think it's it's it's a different dynamic
because you got to think I walk into
Denver as a highest paid quarterback,
you know, make all this money, all all
these things, right? So, so there is
some impact there when I walk in the
door because the expectations are there.
>> But DC, I mean, we hung out A LOT. COME
ON.
DC WAS a problem, man. And I I I got to
I got to say I did not want to leave for
those reasons because the atmosphere
there, I mean, the the fan base, I mean,
this the city, the night life, it was
>> it was amazing. But at the same time,
man, I had to look out. My career was
most important. And I I definitely made
the right decision.
>> It just wasn't I I didn't really want to
leave. It was just I had to do it
business.
>> Yeah. I'm going to say you had to do it.
I LEFT AND CAME RIGHT BACK. YOU LIKE IT
it happen. Yeah, it it happens, man.
When it's that time and it's that
situation, you got to do what's best for
the person and the player. Not, you
know, not trying to make everybody
happy. They always say if you try to
make everybody happy, you make nobody
happy.
>> Yeah.
>> Nobody. You right about that, brother.
>> Champ, when you look at today's game,
who are some of the players you really
enjoy watching, particularly at the
quarterback position?
>> Uh Pat Certan. I mean, and not cuz he's
in Denver. He just he's a technician.
And I I saw it at Bama. So to be able to
see him, you know, go to the Broncos and
play the way he did. And people thought
I was crazy when I was saying this dude
could be a Hall of Famer. I mean, look
at him now. Defensive player of the
year,
>> four, five time Pro Bowler. I mean, he's
on his way. Yeah.
>> Right. He's done it. He's done enough at
this point to at least, you know, get a
lot of votes and probably be first or
second ballot. I mean, that's what he's
done up to now. and the dude's still
young. So, yeah, I'm looking forward to
seeing where he goes. Um, he's
definitely one of my favorites. You
know, another guy, he hadn't even made
it to the league yet is uh Caleb DS.
>> Yeah,
>> kid from Ohio State. Yeah,
>> I can't wait. He He
>> He probably could have came straight out
of high school, went to the pros. That
dude has been the man from day one.
>> Yeah,
>> dog. So, I can't wait to see him get his
career off the ground. When he went to
Bama, I was like, "Oh, yeah. He's three
and done. I don't care. And then he
transferred one and natty. I mean, the
dude is something special, man. So, I'm
I'm looking forward to seeing how his
pro career takes off.
>> I love watching Derek Stingley play the
cornerback position. I And I'm going
tell you this. This a kid in this draft,
McCoy from Tennessee. He is a baller.
All right, champ. Wait, wait till you
see this kid. He didn't play this year
because he had tow his ACL before the
season started. But but he he going he
going first round off his film from last
year. That's how good that this kid is.
Then he just ran a 4340 at his workouts.
This guy can flat out go.
>> Oh okay. Okay. You know another corner
you mentioned Stingling. I love Stingley
ever since LSU days
>> is his counterpart uh Kamari Lasser.
>> Yeah. like
>> dude, I mean
>> I don't I don't think he gets a lot of
credit because of you know, but I think
people starting to take notice. He was a
I think I think I did see him playing in
the Pro Bowl game. So, I'm like, okay,
well, at least they noticing, you know,
this kid is something special. So, and
he's a bulldog, you know, of course.
>> Yeah. I've been saying that's that's why
you brought him in there cuz he a
bulldog. But last going through the the
robin uh effect that I had to go through
playing with you. ALL RIGHT. PLAYING
WITH YOU. YEAH. I HAD TO MAKE PEOPLE
THROW back at you and get and gain my
own respect over there. So, Lassa, I
think Lass, like you said, Lassa getting
his props right now, though.
>> Yeah. I I love it. And and I think some
corners and some corners can't handle
that.
>> Yeah. No, they can't. They can't.
>> You like You got to think You came into
the league in my third year, so I'm
coming off my first Pro Bowl. And I
mean, you saw how I practiced.
>> Yeah.
>> So, so I know. And that's no different
from when I came and Daryl Green was a
guy. Like you got to figure out first of
all how you learn from that person,
>> but then how you how you maximize your
opportunity playing opposite that
person. So it No, it's it's it's a tall
task.
>> Well, and most definitely LIKE YOU SAID,
EVERYBODY JUST AIN'T UP for it.
>> Nah, bro. Nah, but I loved your
confidence though. I mean, that's that's
one thing we ain't have to teach you.
>> No, I I WAS GOOD. I WAS READY TO GO.
LIKE I SAID, ALL I WANTED TO DO IS EARN
the respect. Once I earned the respect,
then we was off and going. We We were
gone. We We We had fun. We I I I enjoyed
It was the best intro I could have had
to the NFL.
>> Yeah, dog. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I ain't
going to lie, man. Not a lot of people
walk in the locker room like that.
>> No, they don't. Are you ready for the
plays, Anna? ALL RIGHT, CALEB K, TEARS
UP. WE GOING TO TAKE YOU DOWN THE MEMORY
LANE, CHAMP. TAKE YOU THROUGH SOME OLD
PLAYS IN THE BERGEN and Gold. DO YOU
REMEMBER THIS PLAY AGAINST ARIZONA?
>> I do vividly. Now, that was David
Boston, one of my draft mates, uh, that
I jumped in front of and caught that
ball. I had three picks this night.
>> Oh, my rookie year.
>> Really? You know what? We had some
battles against David Boston. You
remember we had to get him off of D
Green. He wanted to fight D Green one
time.
>> No, he he wanted to fight everybody at
the time. Remember he came back to uh I
think it was training camp and he WAS
LIKE 240.
>> YES. HE WAS HE WAS HUGE.
>> HE'S HUGE.
>> He ain't 240 right here. Right.
>> Nothing happened in that off season and
he came back my third year. I'll never
forget
>> and he was 240. I'm like man what the
hell you been doing?
>> 240. 240 with red contacts. Yeah. Yes.
Yes. Yes.
>> Something else man.
>> Let's see what we got next. Kayla.
>> Oh, Sam, this me and you playing in this
game. Us against Tio.
>> Okay. Okay. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. We
battled that day. We both got a little
bit of TO0 that day.
>> No. No. We We We got him. We We started
to hand him back and forth. They tried
to match us up with him. Jeff Garcia.
Did they give you Did they GIVE YOU THAT
PICK RIGHT THERE?
>> I CAN'T REMEMBER. I can't I feel like
they did. I can't I can't remember.
>> I don't think I did. I don't maybe I did
pick up there. I got it.
>> Yeah, I WAS GONNA SAY CUZ I FEEL LIKE
YOU GOT TO PICK this guy. I know for a
fact you got to pick this guy.
>> I I don't know. I I remember catching
one in the end zone where I had to jump
up high, but I [__] I could have been
with
>> Yeah, I remember the one in the back of
the
>> kept running together.
>> YEAH. YEAH. I I SAY I THINK IT WAS THE
BACK OF THE ENDZONE INTERCEPTION. I
think they gave it to you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that that's that's
probably true.
>> Yeah.
>> But yeah, man. I remember this game. God
dog boy.
>> Ty streets and who else was out there? I
haven't heard that name in a long time.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. Go to the next place.
>> I remember Smooth. We thought we we
thought we were hot [__] back then.
>> Yeah. Oh yeah. HEY, LISTEN. WE WE DID
THINK WE WAS ON IT. WE WAS ON IT. LIKE
YOU REALIZE IT WASN'T A DUO OUT THERE
JUST just really better than us at the
time, man.
>> Oh, look at that. Look at her. Look at
her. Oh, you so slim. LOOK AT HER.
>> THE SLIM REAPER. I'M TALKING ABOUT
SKINNY AS I CAN BE. Oh my goodness. 150
pounds.
>> Yeah, but I I I can run and I can press.
That was my D. I can I can play press
coverage. I was fine with that. And old
Sam Shady out there. Shady doing good
coaching right now, too.
>> Oh my go Oh, yeah. That's my dog, man.
>> Champ, when you look back at your
career, and of course you can go
highlight after highlight. Is there a
particular player too that for you was
your favorite?
Oh, you know, I I always go back to my
first pick
>> uh
>> in my career because I got Troy Aman and
you gota think I grew up, you know,
loving Troy Aman,
>> idolizing them. Yep.
>> All of them were in that game, too. So,
you had EMTT, uh, Irvin, and Troy all in
that game in my rookie year. First game
of my career,
>> and I picked him. I I let him I let him
know about it every time I see him.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You never you never forget
the first pick cuz I never forget Doug
Fluty when we played them in San Diego.
That was my first game. Oh yeah. Yeah.
>> Fluty. I didn't know that first pick.
>> They were my first pick.
>> Legendary players, dog. When you get
those legendary guys, man, it just means
something different, man.
>> Yeah. You you just you don't forget it
cuz I I WAS SHELL SHOCKED AT FIRST CUZ
YOU STILL STAR STUFF. You still like cuz
I'm watching Junior Sea. I'm like, man,
I think it's two of him out here the way
he balling. Then you got fluted and that
was LT first game cuz we were rookie
together.
>> Oh my god.
>> And that's when I knew he was the real
deal.
>> Kicked our asses.
>> YEAH, HE RAN THAT BALL on us. Boy, it
was a long one, baby. It was a long day.
>> Yeah, man. Man, Chapman man, I
appreciate you coming, man. Thank you
for being on the Get Live show. Can't
wait till you come back up so we can
celebrate you some more, brother.
>> Yeah, let's do this again during the
season, man.
>> All right, we going TO DO IT. I SAY
WE'RE GOING TO DO IT DURING THE SEASON,
MAN. APPRECIATE YOU, BROTHER.
>> Thank you, champ.
>> All right. Good to see you, boy.
>> Always.
>> Let's pay some bills real quick.
Commanders fangeek is the official
primary ticketing partner of Hail to the
Commanders and here to help you
experience all of the action from
football to Funk and any other live
events at Northwest Stadium. Segeek has
the tickets. Segeek is the official
primary ticketing partner of the
Washington Commanders and Northwest
Stadium. And huddle up, Commanders fans.
The Commander Golden Pass Raffle
operated by the Virginia Lottery gives
you the chance to win the ultimate fan
experience. That means tickets, VIP
treatment, special appearances by
Washington Legends, and so much more.
Limited tickets are available, so just
hop online, go to
vaottery.com/commanders
to enter the raffle today. That is
vaulty.com/commanders
and break. Voicemails, emails, Anna?
Yeah, let's let's start with the email.
Um, first email we have is, "Hello, crew
of Get Loud. Lifelong fan. I appreciate
the way that you keep us in touch with
the team. My question is, in evaluating
the OSU defenders, how do you account
for the individual player when the team
has just one dude after another at all
positions? Thanks, Woody from West
Virginia.
>> How do you account for these dudes?"
>> Yeah.
>> First of all, Sunny Styles is one of
one. All right. Bowing to play the game
of football, a middle linebacker. You be
like, "Uh, at seven is that high?" No,
it's not. Sometimes I'll get the player.
>> Yeah,
>> get the player. I don't care. I don't
believe in this draft value stuff.
>> You can't tell me that
>> a a a edge rusher has more value than a
running back,
>> right?
>> I do not want to hear that. You know
why? Because me as an exdefensive
player, I would rather have a better
DTackle than a edge rusher. Okay? the
shortest way to the quarterback is right
through the a
it's more dominant D tackles that have
super bowls than than edge rushers. I
would also say because if you're asking
and I understand I think the idea here
which is okay how could you not be good
there's dudes at every position but I
would flip and say well the reason why
they are that good is because they have
dudes like Arll Reese and Sunny Styles
and Caleb DS like yes there's dudes
everywhere but the reason why as a unit
they're so good is that individually
they're so good
>> they Ohio State has a firstrounder at
every level of his defense
>> at DTackle firstrounder uh edge
linebacker first rounder, defensive
back, firstrounder. Yes, they played off
each other and they played through each
other. Like that's how that defense was
that good, but I don't think you can
lose with drafting. None of them.
>> Yeah.
>> Like Ohio State does this at times. They
just show up at the draft sometime and
be like, just here, take everything we
got to offer right here. We got your
nine first rounders right here. That's
what Ohio State does. Ah, that hurt so
bad coming out. I know. Blue field.
>> Oh my god. And I you've seen that before
where you'll see a guy who maybe plays a
little bit better than he should because
everyone around him is so good. But
these guys aren't like that. They just
individually elevate one another.
>> Yeah. They are individually
talented guys that just happen to be
paying with other talented guys.
Exactly. Yeah. Very things to be true.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. Absolutely.
>> Okay. Next email wasn't really a
question, but it was saying um the
national championship in swimming this
year was won by UV UVA, not Texas.
>> Oh,
>> just to verify.
>> Are you sure?
>> I I Texas won it last year. I want to
say
>> maybe that's what I was thinking.
>> What they say the national championship
is what?
>> Swimming.
>> Texas swimming.
>> Let me see.
>> Am I wrong? I mean, I don't want to take
away from UVA. Um
>> the national championship.
>> Not when it come to sports
>> ship in swimming. I should have looked
this up. I had it and then um okay UVA's
women's and men's won so women's
swimming won the national championship
>> but the men won this year
>> but the men UT
>> yes
>> won this year so that's correct
>> both are true that's you know we have
hit an alltime low when Texas is
reaching for swim championships
>> we have we have reached a a rock bottom
>> what do you mean
>> Texas they brag about football
>> they have so many good sports I hate to
back Jinx up on this.
>> I believe that Texas won the award as or
at least one of two of the most
accomplished athletic program in the
country.
>> Yeah, I was I was looking at like
Mississippi State and they had baseball
like in 2021 or something. Yeah, we won
that championship and then it's been
it's been a while. But in your defense,
Colorado, it's all it's all skiing.
>> No, y'all won nothing.
>> Our last football championship was like
what is it 1990? 199
Stewart Sean was bad.
>> Michael used to be really good.
>> Did you celebrate Denver winning the
Frozen 4, winning the national?
>> I watched it. I They won it last year,
too, which was really exciting. Yeah.
Back to back. So, that was exciting for
them. I I kind of celebrated. I saw it
on the TV and then I was like went on
about my evening. But exciting.
>> I was actually in a bar in DC, last call
in DC, and there was actually a small
group locked in.
>> Oh.
>> To Wisconsin and Denver. And I didn't
know it at first. And all of a sudden, I
hear this roar. It's not a huge place. I
turn around and there's some Denver
hockey fans high-fiving because they
just tied it up in Wisconsin.
>> I'm shocked the Minnesota golfers didn't
win. Pull that thing out.
>> It was the final four were North Dakota,
Wisconsin, Denver, and
>> Michigan. Yeah.
>> Michigan had a hell of a year.
>> Crazy program. Yeah. Oh, last voicemail
and then we'll move on to our top 10.
Okay.
>> Hey, James, Fred, Anna, Kayla, K,
Amanda, the whole crew. How do y'all do?
Fred from Florida, man. Just getting
ready up prepping up for this draft. Uh
the Fred and the Smoodalytics. I love
it, man. This time you become a smooth
aaholic. Anyways, my question is kind of
for both you guys. Uh called the second
rounders, man. Uh we don't have one this
year, but uh Amos,
uh uh Newton, sorry, and set these uh
three guys in the second round. and I
just need to see what your thought is on
what they can bring to the table this
year for us. Anyways, keep up the great
work. Hell to the DMV and the
commanders. Thank you. Love y'all.
>> Appreciate you.
>> This is a big year for uh Ben Senate.
Like Ben S has to turn the corner this
year.
>> Yeah.
>> He has to mature into the player that
they thought he was going to be or that
he should be. This is going to be a big
year for him. Mikey Sage still, he was
one of them second screen, I mean second
uh round guys. I think Mikey gonna have
one of his could be his best year this
year. Like especially with this type
defense we about to play.
>> Isn't this the time when a guy like that
who's kind of had ups and downs but
showing flashes now everything just
flattens out now. Now I I had my good, I
had my bad, I had my ugly. Now I know
what's this league is about. Now let me
go have my best year. Right. So yeah, I
can see him having his best year. Who
was the other Oh,
>> it was uh Jazern Newton was the other
second round. I think Johnny Newton is
ready to rock and roll.
>> Good job using Jon, too.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Because that's that's his
name. THAT'S HIS REAL NAME. IF I'M GOING
TO NAME HIM JON, I'M GONNA CALL HIM JON.
>> All I'm saying is I think last year cuz
I always tell people it take one good
game in this league to to build your
confidence up.
>> And uh that three sack game he had, I
think that just open up the door and let
him know, man, I I can do this every
game.
>> Yeah.
>> So, I'm looking for those guys to really
come into their own. At third year you
own it. Now it's first year rookie
jitters and
>> like you trying to find out do I belong?
Second year I'm trying to make this name
stick in the league. Third year this
mine,
>> right?
>> This mine. So yeah, I'm looking for
these guys to have a a hell of a year
this year. That good? No more? Huh?
Okay. Well, who's going in the top 10?
So we're talking draft here. Everybody's
asking about what's going to happen in
later rounds, you know, with guys we've
drafted. maybe you can get some value
because commanders only have, you know,
two picks in the top 100, right? So,
they got to find the value in those two
picks. But let's talk about the top 10
because there's been some discussion
that maybe because the team doesn't have
>> as many draft picks as they would like
that maybe they trade back and maybe
they get a couple more picks or an extra
pick. Somebody got to want to trade up
first. They go to kicker, man. I think
it's going to happen. Like if somebody
that
All right. Some team has to fall in love
with somebody that they think going in
the top team.
>> Yes.
>> Like that's how this happens. All right.
And the only person I felt could have
tilted this draft and made it awkward
was Tai Simpson.
>> All right.
>> If somebody thinks he is that dude,
>> he can make the draft awkward.
>> He is the odd piece. He is the one that
makes He can make four players slide if
he can win the top 10. like he is the
the the figure head that makes
everything go. Let's just But see, if
I'm the Jets and I got the number two
pick in the what number 16 pick,
>> I don't think Ty Simpson is going before
16.
>> And that's the thing, like if you look,
Vegas, they're going for Fernando
Mendoza. You got Jets, Cardinals,
Titans already have a quarterback,
Giants have a quarterback, Browns have a
quarterback, Manders, you get Saints,
>> they got a quarterback.
>> Yeah. Chiefs and Bengals. So there's not
a whole lot of demand
>> for the good move up.
>> Yeah. So that that go the thing about
you can want to put your car in reverse,
but if it's a car behind you, Yeah. you
can't back up. I That's the thing about
it. We can't back up until somebody want
to pass us. And I don't know if somebody
going to want to pass us cuz for what
player,
>> right? That's the key. The only other
player I could figure somebody would
shoot up the draft for has to be
offensive line.
>> Yeah.
>> Like that. That's the only other
position that I could say could force
somebody hand because the the freakish
athletes,
they gonna be coming off the board.
Okay. And and you're right. The reason
why we're talking about Ty Simpson is
normally it's a quarterback. Normally
those are the dudes that teams trade up
for. Like they need a QB. Everyone loves
a quarterback. Maybe this guy's the new
cornerstone. But outside of that, then
there has to be someone that you covet.
>> And I I just don't know if that guy is
there. But we don't know because draft
boys are funny. like they are very funny
and they it don't take but it's always
gonna be somebody like the Cardinals
that picked a player you be like what
are they doing like why are they doing
it like
>> right
>> so it's going to be a team that make
that why pick like right now if the
Tennessee Titans
coales coach so when you hear defensive
coach first thing you hear figure in
your head like oh they gonna go defense
>> why when they got Cam Ward won't you
want to give him an offensive weapon I
don't think it's to me
>> and their defense isn't terrible by the
way defense. Yeah.
>> But to me,
it's only probably one or two first
round wide receivers in this class to
me.
>> Mhm.
>> I So it ain't the ain't no Jamar Chase
in this class.
>> That's why if at least for the
Commanders, I would I know a lot of
people have said maybe you take Carnell
Tape, but I I think I'd look at a
receiver later.
>> Later. I can get this. I can get that
production later.
>> Exactly. Or something similar to it.
like the value is there because it's a
deeper receiver class.
>> Is he going to be a good pro? I think he
going to be a good pro. Yeah, I think he
going to have very much
cuz he was never the dude dude at Ohio
State. That was Jeremiah Smith. So, I
think he going to have that Terry type
blossom career. Well, he's going to be
maybe the best out of the Ohio State
guys that he had cuz to me Terry was
>> Yeah.
>> He outplayed the other guys that went
first round.
>> So, I I don't know, man. It's all it
takes is one team to fall in love with
you.
>> That's it. That's all.
>> That's it.
>> I mean, just like when we were doing the
draft coverage a couple years ago and
Michael Penn was chosen by the Falcons
and we were just like, all right, he
wasn't supposed to go that high,
especially after they'd signed Kirk and
we were like, I don't know what you guys
are doing.
>> I don't know what they was doing.
>> I mean, so you never know. You just
never know.
>> You never know. Like that's the thing
about the D. I said it's going to be one
team in the top 10 that does something
very funky.
>> Yeah. like they're gonna do something
very funky and I don't know what their
funky is. We got to sit and wait. But at
least the draft is going to be faster
this year. They didn't cut like a minute
off the time.
>> Oh, did they?
>> Between picks.
>> So, it needed to do that.
>> It should be a little tighter.
>> Let me You know what? Since we're
talking about the Falcons for a second,
I asked you earlier which quarterback is
under the most pressure this year.
>> Is Michael Pennock
>> under that pressure? Because he's going
to compete with Tua and if he doesn't
become the starter this year,
>> he going to have to make some plays. And
this these are two lefties. So that's
crazy too.
>> No, that that it is. But they both got
kind of the same problem. The ball kind
of dies on them sometime.
>> Yeah.
>> But I think it's a good competition.
Yeah,
>> cuz I actually think the Falcons are
going to be a good team.
>> Do you?
>> I do. I do really do think they're going
to be a good team.
>> So it is your birthday week and now
because of your birthday, we're going to
play Start Bench and Cut birthday
edition. And Annie, you want to lead us
through here?
>> Sure.
>> All right,
>> you guys come in. It's just a fun little
activity. Start bench cut bar crawl
house party chill dinner.
>> Okay,
>> I think I know.
>> All right. Uh,
cut bar crawl.
>> Start house party. Okay.
>> [__] chill dinner.
>> Wow. I actually wasn't expecting that.
>> I would I would You know what? I thought
you would start bar crawl.
>> No, I like to get at one place and stay
there.
>> That's the way I would cut it, too. Like
when I was younger, the bar crawl is
fun, but once you do it a couple times,
like I just want to send somebody.
>> I'm going here. I'm going to start and
I'm going end here.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. Next. Start bench. Cut pizza,
wings, ribs.
>> Ooh, start ribs. I almost did that.
>> I'm cutting pizza.
>> Yeah, pizza is cut. The wings got to
stay.
>> Yeah,
>> I agree with that. Yeah, that's a good
call. Okay. Start bench cut cake
cupcakes ice cream.
>> Oh,
all right. Uh,
start cake.
Cut cupcakes.
>> Yes.
>> Bench ice cream.
>> Oh, you bench ice cream, though?
>> Yeah. Well, I I still keep it on the
bench.
>> Yeah.
>> But I I cut the cupcake cuz it's
cupcakes to me. uh
overrated.
>> It's the frosting to cake ratio that's
completely
>> Yeah, it's overrated.
>> It's too much frosting. Way too much.
>> Like if I get a good piece of cake.
Okay. I love some ice cream, so I'll
crush some ice cream. But the cupcake,
it's like there's so much frosting
sometimes.
>> I don't look forward to a cupcake.
>> It's like just pure sugar. Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. This one I have It's a two-part
question. Start bench cut. Your like
clutch friend, your funny friend, and
your responsible friend. Now, think
about this is for your birthday party.
>> Oh, all right. I want to start my front
friend cuz it's your birthday. You want
to have fun. That's what it's about. So,
you bring out your loudest friends on
your birthday.
>> Uhhuh.
>> I'm going to cut my responsible friend.
I don't need you to this day.
>> You won't make it home.
>> I got Uber now.
>> That's true. All right.
>> I got Uber. I DON'T NEED HIM. STAY YOUR
BORED BUTT at home. Right.
>> This ain't your day. I'mma call you on a
on Sunday when we go to church.
>> Yeah.
>> Now I don't need you.
>> All right. I I don't need you. Clutch
friend.
>> Bench.
>> Yeah. On.
>> Okay. Who's who?
>> Who is the friends?
>> Yeah. We don't have to say who the
responsible friend is if you don't want
to. But that's a compliment even though
you're cutting them from your book.
>> I can say this. Sean is very
responsible. Sean Springs is uber
responsible.
>> He is.
>> I get no really. Now, he's reckless in
some fashions, okay?
>> But when it come
>> when it come to handling business,
>> Sean is very much very responsible.
>> Uh I think uh London is funnier than
people think.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. London is way funnier than to go
in on you, man.
>> And Tanner is clutch.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Like you can hit Tana up any time of the
night. Where you at? Come get me. I got
you. Like you you ain't got to worry
about it.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Last one. Start bench cut. Oh my
god.
>> Pumpkin, raisins, warm milk.
>> First of all, the first two. Cut, cut,
cut.
>> No, you have to pick. You have to pick.
>> Cut.
Pumpkin.
>> You You just hate pumpkin.
>> I hate It's useless, man. See, one thing
I love, the one thing I can say about a
raisin, it used to be a grape.
>> I thought you were definitely going to
cut raisins here.
>> No. No. Grape.
>> I thought so, too.
>> Raisins used to be a a voluupuous sweet
grape
>> and a shrimp.
In its first form, it's everything you
want.
>> All right. A pumpkin in it first form, I
still don't want it.
>> All right. Nobody likes pumpkin. All
right. Pumpkin useless. All right. So,
most definitely I keep the warm milk.
I mean,
>> none of these choices are great. In my
head, I was like, "Yeah, I don't know,
man."
>> Yeah. Listen, I'm just keeping it 100,
man. Listen, pumpkins are just it, man.
I'm going tell you how bad pumpkins is.
People just sit them on the porch, cut a
face in them,
let them sit there for months.
>> That's true.
>> Even the squirrel don't like it.
>> Well, man, I knew all all I knew is just
going to take one mention of pumpkin and
this was going to lose his mind.
>> But this solidified it that you cut it
out the box, kept raising.
>> Woo! Guys, don't forget tomorrow,
Franklin Hall uniform reveal YouTube x
Facebook. Hit the little bell
notification on YouTube to remind you if
you can't make it so you can watch live.
I'll be there. He's going to be there. I
might DROP BY. YEAH, WHY NOT? IT'S IN
YOUR NEIGHBORHOOD. I I walk there. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. He'll see you there.
>> The Get Loud podcast was filmed at the
Big Bear AI command center studios. Big
Bear AI offers mission ready AI for
rapidly evolving world and proudly
protecting the Washington Commanders and
his fans.
The views and opinions expressed by our
podcast guests and/or hosts are their
own and do not necessarily reflect the
views or positions of the Washington
Commanders or any of their
representatives.